

Info

29.10.1999 +994(55) 992 44 01

vasiyevsamil@gmail.com

Baku, Azerbaijan

https://github.com/shamilvasiyev

Skills

HTML5

Css3

Bootstrap

JavaScript

React

NodeJS

Express.js

MongoDB

Mongoose

Education

Bachelor's Degree

UNEC

Accounting & Audit

2016 - 2020

Course

Orient ITM

Front End Development Aug 2020 - Feb 2021

Personal Values

Responsibility
Punctuality
Creativity
Innovation
Cooperation
Huminity
Flexibility

Shamil Vasiyev

Front End Developer

Profil

Front-end web developer with 2 years of experience developing user interfaces in real project with HTML, Css, JavaScript and Reactjs and also I have additional information Node JS(Express.js), MongoDB(Mongoose)

I have good practice and working closely with the UI team to match beautiful designs with well-written code

Employment History

Mover.az

Front End Developer (internship) May 2021 - Nov 2021

- Enjoyed being with a professional team.
- Understood how development and business cycles work.
- Turning the prepared designs into web pages by adapting to the grid structure.
- Using javascript framework (React)
- Project development with the backend team.

Oyuncaqli.az

MERN Stack Developer (freelance)

Okt 2022 - Dec 2022

- A website developed for online toy sales.
- Front-end side is developed with React.
- Node js(Express.js) and Mongo DB(Mongoose) are used in the development of the back-end and database part.

Weather app

Front End Developer (project)

- The daily weather conditions of more than 200 cities around the world can be viewed.
- Beautiful pictures of the searched city are displayed in the background.
- The project was developed via React

Shopping website

Front End Developer (project)

- Responsive, online shopping website developed with React